Guide to the Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
- Series III: Confessions O-T
  - Names: P
    - Prey Sdo Leang, N/A (Reel 120, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/1/1975; 31/7/1976(2); 1/8/1976(3); 3/8/1976(2); 4/8/1976; 5/8/1976(3); 7/8/1976(2); 8/8/1976(3); 9/8/1976(3)
      10/8/1976(6); 1/8/1976(3); 13/8/1976(4); 14/8/1976; 2 sections undated
    - Prey Sreut, 8/1977 (Reel 117, Frame 16)
    - Prich Men, 18/5/1977 (Reel 106, Frame 25)
    - Pril Kuy, 1/9/1977 (Reel 118, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/9/1977; 15/11/1977
    - Prim Moul, N/A (Reel 120, Frame 8)
    - Prim Yim, 13/10/1977 (Reel 118, Frame 7)
    - Pro Ban, 12/6/1977 (Reel 110, Frame 13)
    - Proeng Lann, N/A (Reel 119, Frame 11)
    - Proenh Chreng, 10/1977 (Reel 124, Frame 1)
    - Proeurng Pram, N/A (Reel 108, Frame 19)
    - Proeurng Vorn, 1/9/1977 (Reel 107, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/9/1977; 18/10/1977; 8/9/1977
    - Prok Chun, 14/1/1978 (Reel 121, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/1/1978; 23/2/1978; 1 section undated
    - Prok Dam, 9/1977 (Reel 117, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/3/1977
    - Prok Hel, N/A (Reel 121, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/12/1976; 4/12/1976(3); 5/12/1976(2); 8/12/1976(2)
    - Prok Tre, 19/3/1977 (Reel 123, Frame 28)
    - Prom Nho, N/A (Reel 109, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/10/1976(3); 28/10/1976; 23/10/1976 (2); 2/11/1976; 21/11/1976; 29/10/1976; 31/10/1976; 31/12/1976; 3/11/1976; 5/11/1976; 6/11/1976; 7/11/1976(2)
      9/11/1976(2); 13/11/1976; 10/11/1976; 16/11/1976; 18/1/1976(2)
      15/11/1976; 14/11/1976; 22/11/1976; 25/11/1976; 26/11/1976
      31/11/1976; 30/11/1976
    - Pronh Sam Uon, N/A (Reel 122, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/12/1976; 8/12/1976; 9/12/1976; 14/12/1976(2); 16/12/1976; 22/12/1976; 23/12/1976; 23/12/1976; 25/12/1976; 2/1/1977; 3/1/1977(2)
    - Prosoeut Lorpkaeut, 21/12/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 38)
    - Prou Srun, N/A (Reel 110, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/10/1976; 18/10/1976; 19/10/1976; 28/10/1976; 29/10/1976; 30/10/1976(2); 12/10/1976(3); 10/10/1976(3); 11/10/1976; 27/10/1976; 21/10/1976(3); 21/10/1976(2)
      20/10/1976(2); 22/10/76(2)
    - Proy Ky, 16/5/1977 (Reel 120, Frame 4)
    - Prum Chhuon, N/A (Reel 123, Frame 7)
    - Prum Chy, 16/8/1977 (Reel 108, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/1/1978; 2/3/1978
    - Prum Duong, 4/11/1975 (Reel 109, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/11/1975; 16/2/1976; 11/1975; 1 section undated
    - Prum Hor, N/A (Reel 107, Frame 10)
    - Prum Khoeurn, N/A (Reel 117, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/1975; 4 sections undated
    - Prum Kim Choeurn, 10/1/1976 (Reel 106, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/5/1976; 12/1/1976
    - Prum Kim Van, 15/8/1977 (Reel 107, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/9/1977; 6/11/1977
    - Prum Kuoy, N/A (Reel 108, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/1/1977
    - Prum Kuy Sreng, 8/1977 (Reel 111, Frame 11)
    - Prum Ky, 30/11/1976 (Reel 116, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/1/1977; 27/6/1977
    - Prum Lor, 7/1977/ (Reel 111, Frame 1)
    - Prum Man, 11/12/1976 (Reel 111, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/12/1976; 4/2/1977; 24/1/1977; 19/12/1976; 1 section undated
    - Prum Me, 10/1976 (Reel 111, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/11/1976(2); 6/11/1976(2); 10/11/1976; 14/11/1976; 15/11/1976; 20/11/1976; 23/11/1976; 26/11/1976; 30/11/1976; 3/12/1976; 8/12/1976
    - Prum Monn, 24/8/1978 (Reel 119, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/10/1978
    - Prum Nget, 14/8/1977 (Reel 123, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/10/1977; 27/9/1977
    - Prum Nhar, 3/1977 (Reel 119, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/3/1977; 23/3/1977; 29/3/1977(2)
    - Prum Nun, N/A (Reel 123, Frame 12)
    - Prum Oeurn, N/A (Reel 108, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/8/1976(2); 21/8/1976; 27/8/1976
    - Prum Phal, N/A (Reel 116, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/12/1978; 6/12/1978; 11/12/1978
    - Prum Phanh, N/A (Reel 106, Frame 8)
    - Prum Phat, N/A (Reel 116, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/2/1977; 6/2/1977; 8/2/1977; 12/2/1977; 26/2/1977
    - Prum Phat, 10/3/1978 (Reel 121, Frame 20)
    - Prum Phoeurn, 12/1/1977 (Reel 124, Frame 20)
    - Prum Phorn, N/A (Reel 123, Frame 17)
    - Prum Preang, 1/1978 (Reel 122, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/2/1978; 3/3/1978; 1 section undated
    - Prum Ry, 18/3/1978 (Reel 108, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/5/1978
    - Prum Ry, 18/3/1978 (Reel 111, Frame 12)
    - Prum Sa, 28/1/1978 (Reel 111, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/4/1978; 2/2/1978; 6/5/1978; 1/2/1978; 5/3/1978; 16/4/1978; 22/2/1978; 5/3/1978; 1 section undated
    - Prum Samneang, N/A (Reel 116, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/9/1975; 10/9/1975; 12/9/1975; 8/10/1976
    - Prum San, N/A (Reel 118, Frame 14)
    - Prum Sao, 6/1977 (Reel 111, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/8/1977; 1 section undated
    - Prum Saray, 1/2/1976 (Reel 109, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/2/1977; 18/2/1977
    - Prum Seang, N/A (Reel 116, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/1/1977
    - Prum Sin, 11/7/1977 (Reel 107, Frame 6)
    - Prum Sinavuth, 15/3/1976 (Reel 105, Frame 43)
    - Prum Soeurn, N/A (Reel 105, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/9/1976; 26/9/1976(2)
    - Prum Sok, N/A (Reel 106, Frame 6)
    - Prum Sothear, 1/2/1978 (Reel 121, Frame 2)
    - Prum Suang, 4/11/1978 (Reel 124, Frame 22)
    - Prum Suth, 8/2/1978 (Reel 121, Frame 25)
    - Prum Tem, N/A (Reel 122, Frame 23)
    - Prum Thuch, 11/1/1976 (Reel 106, Frame 13)
    - Prum Thy, N/A (Reel 123, Frame 32)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/2/1978; 1 section undated
    - Prum Tim, N/A (Reel 111, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/1/1977
    - Prum Vat, 24/12/1976 (Reel 106, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/2/1977; 6/2/1977; 5/2/1977; 4/2/1977; 3/2/1977
    - Prum Yon, N/A (Reel 107, Frame 16)
    - Pu Ram, 8/1977 (Reel 106, Frame 12)
    - Pum Lai, 3/1977 (Reel 120, Frame 21)
    - Pum Pil, N/A (Reel 107, Frame 19)
    - Put Kaing, 10/1977 (Reel 124, Frame 36)
    - Put Thon, 31/12/1977 (Reel 124, Frame 4)
    - Put Y, 25/6/1977 (Reel 122, Frame 16)
    - Puth, N/A (Reel 117, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/11/1992
    - Puth Eng, 7/1/1977 (Reel 120, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/2/1977; 19/2/1977; 7/1/1977
    - Puy Tay Ny, 23/2/1977 (Reel 105, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/2/1977; 24/2/1977; 5/3/1977; 6/3/1977; 5/3/1977; 7/3/1977; 1 section undated
  - Names: Q
    - Qaung Boeurn, 29/3/1977 (Reel 25, Frame 5)
    - Qum Chauven, 24/1/1977 (Reel 105, Frame 25)
  - Names: R
    - Raing Doeurm, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 20)
    - Raing Vueng, 13/11/1977 (Reel 125, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/11/1977; 2/12/1977
    - Ran Chet, 14/12/1977 (Reel 127, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/2/1978; 6/5/1978
    - Rang Korn, N/A (Reel 125, Frame 6)
    - Ras Buok, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/12/1978; 9/12/1978
    - Rat Leang, 1/12/1978 (Reel 127, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/12/1978; 18/12/1978
    - Rath Hun, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 37)
    - Rath La, 14/1/1978 (Reel 126, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/2/1978(2)
    - Rath Ngam, N/A (Reel 126, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/1/1977
    - Ra'Th Phy, 11/1977 (Reel 126, Frame 14)
    - Rath Srun, 1/7/1976 (Reel 127, Frame 3)
    - Ray Roeurn, 1/1978 (Reel 126, Frame 10)
    - Re Sim, 24/8/1977 (Reel 127, Frame 1)
    - Real Bour, 30/1/1978 (Reel 127, Frame 23)
    - Real Link, 27/3/1977 (Reel 127, Frame 35)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/5/1977; 8/6/1977
    - Reay Reum, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 22)
    - Rem Nhep, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 21)
    - Ren Rum, 9/8/1977 (Reel 126, Frame 3)
    - Rim Poeurn, 4/12/1978 (Reel 127, Frame 41)
    - Rin, N/A (Reel 125, Frame 2)
    - Rith Hoeurn, 30/1/1977 (Reel 125, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/2/1977; 12/2/1977; 15/2/1977; 1 section undated
    - Rith Norl, 23/11/1977 (Reel 127, Frame 34)
    - Rith Roeurn, 18/2/1977 (Reel 126, Frame 9)
    - Rith Rum, 2/1978 (Reel 127, Frame 18)
    - Rith Yoeurn, 11/2/1978 (Reel 127, Frame 38)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/3/1978
    - Roch Reth, 23/11/1976 (Reel 125, Frame 5)
    - Roeung Leng, N/A (Reel 126, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/12/1975; 20/12/1975
    - Roeurn Lun, 30/10/1977 (Reel 126, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/5/1978; 5/12/1977
    - Roeurn Orth, N/A (Reel 126, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/8/1977; 13/8/1977; 18/9/1977; 25/8/1977
    - Roeurn Rum, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 12)
    - Roeurng Hort, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 33)
    - Ronald Keith Dean, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 54)
      Nationality (if foreign): CIA/British Nationality
    - Rong Pech, 2/9/1977 (Reel 127, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/12/1977
    - Ros Ang, 23/5/1978 (Reel 126, Frame 12)
    - Ros Chheang, 31/12/1977 (Reel 127, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/2/1978; 5/1/1978
    - Ros Chun, 31/12/1977 (Reel 127, Frame 39)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/1/1978
    - Ros Han, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 11)
    - Ros Khchoung, 17/8/1977 (Reel 127, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/8/1977
    - Ros Khoeurn, 15/7/1977 (Reel 127, Frame 32)
    - Ros Leang, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/12/1975
    - Ros Leang, 1/1976 (Reel 127, Frame 9)
    - Ros Mao, 27/6/1977 (Reel 125, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/7/1977; 14/7/1977; 2 sections undated
    - Ros Nheam, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/1/1977; 22/1/1977
    - Ros Noeurn, 21/6/1978 (Reel 127, Frame 13)
    - Ros Pak, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/1/1976
    - Ros Phat, 25/1/1977 (Reel 126, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/2/1977(3)
    - Ros Phornn, N/A (Reel 125, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/8/1976; 25/8/1976(2); 26/8/1976; 29/8/1976; 29/9/1976(2); 20/9/1976; 30/9/1976; 1/10/1976
    - Ros Phuon, N/A (Reel 125, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/7/1976(3); 5/7/1976; 10/7/1976(3); 11/7/1976; 18/7/1976; 12/7/1976; 13/7/1976; 14/7/1976; 15/7/1976; 17/7/1976; 1 section undated
    - Ros Saing, 10/8/1977 (Reel 125, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/8/1977; 28/9/1977; 16/10/1977
    - Ros Sam Oeurn, 12/9/1976 (Reel 125, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/10/1976; 12/10/1976; 15/10/1976; 18/9/1976; 26/9/1976(2); 28/11/1976; 1/12/1976; 4/12/1976; 5/12/1976
      6/12/1976; 13/12/1976; 14/12/1976; 15/12/1976; 16/12/1976; 17/12/1976
    - Ros Saman, 12/2/1978 (Reel 127, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/2/1978; 12/3/1978
    - Ros San, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/10/1975; 5/11/1975
    - Ros Sarin, 12/12/1976 (Reel 125, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/1/1977(2)
    - Ros Sarou, 8/11/1976 (Reel 125, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/11/1976; 20/11/1976; 11/1976; 21/11/1976; 23/11/1976; 24/11/1976; 25/11/1976; 26/11/1976; 27/11/1976; 28/11/1976
      30/11/1976; 1/12/1976; 2/12/1976; 3/12/1976; 4/12/1976; 5/12/1976(2)
      6/12/1976; 7/12/1976; 24/12/1976(4); 25/12/1976(9); 4 sections undated
    - Ros Seam, 17/2/1977 (Reel 126, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/1977; 4/3/1977; 10/3/1977; 11/3/1977; 11/1/1977; 8/5/1977; 1 section undated
    - Ros Serei Sambun, 7/12/1975 (Reel 127, Frame 14)
    - Ros Sip, 24/8/1977 (Reel 127, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/11/1977
    - Ros So, 6/6/1978 (Reel 127, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/7/1978
    - Ros Sok Lak, 6/10/1975 (Reel 126, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/10/1975; 23/10/ 77 (2); 5;11;75
    - Ros Sok Ly, 4/2/1978 (Reel 127, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/4/1978; 15/4/1978
    - Ros Suon, 19/3/1978 (Reel 125, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/5/1978
    - Ros Than, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 7)
    - Ros Theng, 8/11/1976 (Reel 126, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/12/1976; 11/12/1976' 15/12/1976; 22/12/1976; 26/12/1976; 15/1/1977; 22/1/1977; 24/1/1977; 1/4/1977
    - Ros Thim, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/2/1977(2); 1 section undated
    - Ros Tine, 1/1977 (Reel 126, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/10/1977; 22/10/1977
    - Ros Touch, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 16)
    - Ros Touch, 23/10/1978 (Reel 127, Frame 36)
    - Ros Vann, 29/9/1975 (Reel 127, Frame 4)
    - Ros Yen, 6/1/1978 (Reel 126, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/1/1978; 14/1/1978
    - Roth Than, N/A (Reel 125, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/6/1978; 8/6/1978
    - Roum (Rouin ) Bernard, 15/4/1976 (Reel 185, Frame 51)
      Nationality (if foreign): France
    - Roun Savy, N/A (Reel 126, Frame 8)
    - Roun Than, 19/9/1977 (Reel 126, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/9/1976; 30/9/1976(6); 24/9/1976(5); 3/10/1976(5); 28/9/1978(2); 27/9/1976(4); 2/10/1976(2); 29/9/1976(2); 25/9/1976(2)
    - Roy Netnokrase, 26/12/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 39)
      Nationality (if foreign): Thaas Island
    - Rum Khlaun, 30/7/1978 (Reel 127, Frame 40)
    - Ruon Math, N/A (Reel 127, Frame 31)
    - Ry Chhy, N/A (Reel 126, Frame 7)
  - Names: S
    - Names: Sa
      - Sa Hatt, 6/9/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 45)
      - Sa Khan, 29/8/1978 (Reel 148, Frame 6)
        Dates of Confessions: 5/10/1978
      - Sa Lay, 6/1/1977 (Reel 155, Frame 16)
        Dates of Confessions: 19/1/1977; 22/1/1977; 24/1/1977(2)
      - Sa Leach, N/A (Reel 149, Frame 7)
      - Sa Math, 11/1975 (Reel 156, Frame 12)
        Dates of Confessions: 17/11/1975
      - Sa Neou, N/A (Reel 130, Frame 14)
        Dates of Confessions: 23/6/1977; 29/6/1977
      - Sa Reurm, 1/9/1978 (Reel 154, Frame 23)
      - Sa Rin, 22/8/1977 (Reel 149, Frame 10)
        Dates of Confessions: 22/8/1977
      - Sa Sareth, N/A (Reel 147, Frame 7)
      - Sa Son, N/A (Reel 146, Frame 1)
      - Sa Son, N/A (Reel 154, Frame 21)
      - Sa Thaem, 17/11/1977 (Reel 151, Frame 10)
      - Sa Vancan, N/A (Reel 147, Frame 1)
      - Saem Tak, N/A (Reel 141, Frame 16)
      - Saet Say, 1/8/1977 (Reel 152, Frame 11)
        Dates of Confessions: 9/1/1977; 10/8/1977
      - Saing Khan, 20/1/1977 (Reel 157, Frame 15)
        Dates of Confessions: 29/1/1977; 20/1/1977; 2/2/1977(2); 8/2/1977(2); 11/3/1977; 20/2/1977
      - Saing Moeurng, N/A (Reel 132, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 21/9/1976(5); 30/9/1976(6); 19/9/1976(40; 26/9/1976(2); 27/9/1976(7); 25/9/1976(5); 22/9/1976(2); 24/9/1976(2)
        28/9/1976; 4/10/1976
      - Saing Saroeurn, 9/1977 (Reel 128, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 3/3/1977; 27/3/1977; 24/4/1977; 3/9/1977; 1 section undated
      - Sak Man, 15/9/1977 (Reel 157, Frame 7)
        Dates of Confessions: 26/9/1977; 16/10/1977
      - Sakim, 27/5/1978 (Reel 141, Frame 19)
        Dates of Confessions: 2/8/1978
      - Salai Heng, 4/10/1976 (Reel 147, Frame 12)
      - Saless Heat, 18/6/1978 (Reel 156, Frame 10)
      - Saly, 28/3/1978 (Reel 156, Frame 16)
        Dates of Confessions: 11/4/1978
      - Sam, N/A (Reel 144, Frame 15)
        Dates of Confessions: 13/7/1975; 16/9/1975
      - Sam At, N/A (Reel 158, Frame 20)
        Dates of Confessions: 7/3/1977; 8/3/1977; 20/2/1977
      - Sam Chhoeurn, 19/2/1977 (Reel 137, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 7/2/1977; 23/2/1977; 24/2/1977; 1/3/1977; 2/3/1977; 3/3/1977; 4/3/1977; 5/3/1977; 5/5/1977(2); 12/3/1977
        2/4/1977; 9/4/1977; 12/4/1977
      - Sam Chhoeurt, N/A (Reel 129, Frame 2)
      - Sam Chim, 2/6/1978 (Reel 157, Frame 28)
      - Sam Chy, 12/1977 (Reel 137, Frame 12)
      - Sam Hean, N/A (Reel 141, Frame 3)
        Dates of Confessions: 5/12/1976
      - Sam Hom, N/A (Reel 133, Frame 4)
        Dates of Confessions: 9/2/1977; 10/2/1977(2); 2 sections undated
      - Sam Hun, 7/1975 (Reel 141, Frame 10)
        Dates of Confessions: 22/1/1976
      - Sam Huoy, 23/5/1978 (Reel 144, Frame 3)
        Dates of Confessions: 3/6/1978; 11/6/1978
      - Sam Kheat, N/A (Reel 136, Frame 6)
      - Sam Khoeurn, N/A (Reel 153, Frame 9)
        Dates of Confessions: 16/10/1976; 19/10/1976; 20/10/1976; 25/10/1976; 28/10/1976; 8/11/1976; 11/11/1976; 16/10/1976
      - Sam Kin, 3/10/1977 (Reel 158, Frame 12)
        Dates of Confessions: 4/6/1978
      - Sam Ky, N/A (Reel 130, Frame 6)
      - Sam Man, 20/7/1978 (Reel 151, Frame 2)
        Dates of Confessions: 23/8/1978
      - Sam Met, 2/1978 (Reel 141, Frame 18)
      - Sam Moeurn, 11/2/1978 (Reel 158, Frame 22)
      - Sam Nhak, N/A (Reel 151, Frame 17)
      - Sam Ol, 4/5/1978 (Reel 129, Frame 6)
        Dates of Confessions: 17/8/1978; 2/7/1978
      - Sam On, N/A (Reel 155, Frame 25)
        Dates of Confessions: 4/1/1977; 12/2/1977
      - Sam Onn, 15/1/1978 (Reel 143, Frame 10)
      - Sam Phoern, N/A (Reel 151, Frame 18)
      - Sam Phum, 28/1/1978 (Reel 154, Frame 24)
      - Sam Phy, 10/1975 (Reel 140, Frame 15)
      - Sam Pum, N/A (Reel 133, Frame 7)
        Dates of Confessions: 18/8/1976; 10/7/1976; 11/7/1976; 12/7/1976; 15/7/1976; 19/7/1976; 30/7/1976
      - Sam Reth, 4/2/1978 (Reel 156, Frame 21)
        Dates of Confessions: 12/2/1978; 26/2/1978
      - Sam Reth Chak, 7/1975 (Reel 156, Frame 29)
      - Sam San, N/A (Reel 136, Frame 16)
      - Sam Sapolt, N/A (Reel 130, Frame 8)
      - Sam Sarom, 10/3/1977 (Reel 132, Frame 16)
        Dates of Confessions: 7/8/1977; 8/10/1977; 25/10/1977
      - Sam Sarom, 14/3/1977 (Reel 156, Frame 20)
        Dates of Confessions: 15//5/1977
      - Sam Sary, N/A (Reel 150, Frame 14)
        Dates of Confessions: 19/11/1975
      - Sam Shan, 5/5/1977 (Reel 147, Frame 19)
      - Sam Sith, N/A (Reel 151, Frame 13)
      - Sam Than, N/A (Reel 129, Frame 10)
      - Sam Vean, 1/1/1978 (Reel 155, Frame 19)
        Dates of Confessions: 5/1/1978
      - Sam Voeurn, 8/2/1978 (Reel 154, Frame 32)
      - Sam Yun, 12/2/1978 (Reel 146, Frame 22)
        Dates of Confessions: 4/2/1978; 6/3/1978(2)
      - Samas Karim, N/A (Reel 152, Frame 18)
      - Samath, N/A (Reel 152, Frame 14)
      - Sambo Sophat, 19/6/1977 (Reel 128, Frame 7)
        Dates of Confessions: 14/6/1977; 6/8/1977; 27/8/1977
      - Sameth, N/A (Reel 138, Frame 15)
      - Samreth Khem, 5/9/1975 (Reel 154, Frame 11)
      - Samreth Lam Nhaeng, 24/1/1976 (Reel 131, Frame 11)
        Dates of Confessions: 13/10/1975; 16 sections undated
      - Samreth Sokhan, 7/5/1978 (Reel 141, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 5/1978
      - Samreth Vong, 2/1977 (Reel 157, Frame 3)
        Dates of Confessions: 6/3/1977; 7/3/1977(2); 8/3/1977; 9/3/1977; 4/3/1977; 12/3/1977; 13/3/1977; 14/3/1977;15/3/1977; 15/3/1977(2)
      - Samrit Gy, 4/8/1977 (Reel 152, Frame 12)
        Dates of Confessions: 17/8/1977
      - Samrith Ghan, N/A (Reel 148, Frame 10)
      - San, N/A (Reel 138, Frame 2)
        Dates of Confessions: 2/12/1977; 29/12/1977; 1 section undated
      - San, N/A (Reel 150, Frame 16)
      - San, N/A (Reel 151, Frame 25)
        Dates of Confessions: 31/7/1976
      - San An, N/A (Reel 144, Frame 19)
      - San Dim, 4/3/1977 (Reel 146, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 5/2/1977; 6/3/1976(19); 7/3/1977(26); 8/3/1977(21); 10/3/1977(17); 11/3/1977(23); 12/3/1977(2)
      - San Hok, N/A (Reel 152, Frame 16)
      - San Mak, 23/10/1977 (Reel 138, Frame 12)
        Age: 72
      - San Pa, N/A (Reel 148, Frame 18)
      - San Phal, N/A (Reel 158, Frame 16)
      - San Rong, 3/3/1977 (Reel 137, Frame 6)
        Dates of Confessions: 16/3/1977; 28/3/1977; 29/3/1977; 18/4/1977; 27/4/1977
      - San Sarin, N/A (Reel 134, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 29/7/1976
      - San Sim, 10/6/1978 (Reel 132, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 9/7/1978; 28/6/1978
      - San Song, 3/8/1978 (Reel 136, Frame 17)
      - San Sryτan, 25/5/1978 (Reel 151, Frame 4)
      - San Than, N/A (Reel 147, Frame 18)
        Dates of Confessions: 17/1/1977; 18/1/1977; 20/1/1977(2); 21/1/1977; 22/1/1977; 23/1/1977(2); 21/1/1977
      - San That, N/A (Reel 131, Frame 6)
      - San Yem, 3/7/1976 (Reel 158, Frame 2)
        Dates of Confessions: 4/8/1976; 5/8/1976(3); 6/8/1976(6); 8/8/1976(6); 9/8/1976(8); 10/8/1976(9)
      - Sanin, 19/5/1977 (Reel 153, Frame 6)
      - Sann Bun Hy, 21/3/1978 (Reel 140, Frame 8)
        Dates of Confessions: 4/6/1978(2)
      - Sann Leng, N/A (Reel 152, Frame 22)
      - Sann Leng, 27/6/1977 (Reel 156, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 22/7/1977; 16/8/1977
      - Sann Po, 28/7/1978 (Reel 135, Frame 5)
      - Sann Sam At, 8/7/1978 (Reel 141, Frame 9)
      - Sann Seap, 21/4/1977 (Reel 142, Frame 7)
        Dates of Confessions: 11/8/1977; 12/9/1977
      - Sann Soeurn, 11/3/1977 (Reel 138, Frame 14)
      - Sann Sorn, 20/9/1977 (Reel 135, Frame 19)
        Dates of Confessions: 14/2/1978; 7/3/1978
      - Sann Sorn, 20/9/1977 (Reel 152, Frame 32)
        Dates of Confessions: 15/10/1977
      - Sann Thin, 10/12/1977 (Reel 144, Frame 13)
        Dates of Confessions: 13/12/1977; 23/1/1978
      - Sann Voeun, 2/2/1978 (Reel 158, Frame 23)
        Dates of Confessions: 20/2/1978; 12/2/1978
      - Sante Ngin Yuong, 10/4/1978 (Reel 140, Frame 10)
      - Sao Cheang, 1/1978 (Reel 155, Frame 20)
        Dates of Confessions: 9/1/1978
      - Sao Chhann, N/A (Reel 129, Frame 5)
      - Sao Chhay, 15/6/1978 (Reel 152, Frame 7)
        Dates of Confessions: 6/7/1978; 29/7/19789
      - Sao Chhean, 24/5/1978 (Reel 136, Frame 8)
      - Sao Chheng, 27/9/1976 (Reel 154, Frame 20)
        Dates of Confessions: 19/10/1976
      - Sao Chheng, 27/9/1976 (Reel 154, Frame 20)
      - Sao Deth, 16/2/1976 (Reel 142, Frame 3)
      - Sao Kang, 13/12/1976 (Reel 141, Frame 20)
        Dates of Confessions: 6/1/1977; 13/1/1977; 18/1/1977; 10/2/1977; 17/2/1977; 17/5/1977; 13/12/1977; 14/12/1976
      - Sao Kea, N/A (Reel 139, Frame 4)
      - Sao Khun, 2/1977 (Reel 146, Frame 11)
        Dates of Confessions: 8/6/1977; 9/6/1977(54); 10/6/1977(2); 4/7/1977(5); 6/7/1977(7); 7/7/1977(2); 8/7/1977(7); 9/7/1977(6); 10/7/1977(7); 12/7/1977(13); 13/7/1977
        14/7/1977; 27/7/1977(5); 28/7/1977(11); 29/7/1977(9)
      - Sao Kun, N/A (Reel 150, Frame 25)
      - Sao Lan, 30/4/1978 (Reel 150, Frame 18)
      - Sao Man, 1/9/1975 (Reel 143, Frame 18)
        Dates of Confessions: 12/3/1976; 25/12/1978
      - Sao Oeurn, 27/5/1976 (Reel 133, Frame 5)
        Dates of Confessions: 11/6/1976
      - Sao Peng, 27/10/1976 (Reel N/A, Frame N/A)
        Dates of Confessions: 9/10/1976; 9/11/1976(2); 11/11/1976; 13/11/1976; 14/11/1976; 19/11/1976(2); 20/11/1976(3); 23/11/1976; 25/11/1976; 28/11/1976; 29/11/1976
        6/12/1976; 8/12/1976; 28/12/1976; 1/1/1977; 2/1/1977; 4/1/1977
        7/1/1977; 12/1/1977; 15/1/1977(2)
      - Sao Sakhan, 30/12/1977 (Reel 136, Frame 19)
        Dates of Confessions: 15/1/1978; 31/1/1977
      - Sao San, 11/11/1978 (Reel 147, Frame 1)
        Dates of Confessions: 27/11/1978; 16/12/1978; 18/12/1978
      - Sao San, 10/8/1977 (Reel 147, Frame 11)
        Age: 70
      - Sao Sarun, 7/4/1978 (Reel 146, Frame 13)
        Dates of Confessions: 7/4/1978; 24/5/1978
      - Sao Say, 2/5/1977 (Reel 154, Frame 31)
      - Sao Say, 18/1/1978 (Reel 158, Frame 24)
      - Sao Sen, 9/10/1976 (Reel 128, Frame 2)
        Dates of Confessions: 20/10/1976; 23/10/1976; 1/11/1976; 5/11/1976; 4/11/1976; 9/11/1976; 10/11/1976; 22/11/1976; 12/11/1976; 19/11/1976; 26/11/1976
      - Sao Sok, N/A (Reel 143, Frame 17)
        Dates of Confessions: 28/5/1975; 8/1/1976
      - Sao Sokhon, 8/9/1976 (Reel 130, Frame 2)
        Dates of Confessions: 1/12/1976; 3/11/1976; 3/11/1976; 13/11/1976; 14/11/1976; 16/11/1976(2); 19/4/1976; 20/11/1976(3); 21/11/1976(2); 22/11/1976(3) 19/11/1976(2)
        23/11/1976(4)' 24/11/1976(2);; 23/11/1976; 26/11/1976(2); 27/11/1976
        28/11/1976(2); 29/11/1976(2); 30/11/1976(2); 31/11/1976; 2/12/1976(2)
        4/12/1976; 5/12
      - Sao Sokhon, 7/3/1977 (Reel 140, Frame 3)